[{"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " well, y\u0092know i was thinking of moving the couch over here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  why would you want to do that?", "answer": " so that there will be a decent place for me to sit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " rach, there is a decent place to\u009a", "answer": " and your lap does not count! okay? come on help me move this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " no. no. no.", "answer": " no?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " no. rosita does not move.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry, rosita? as in\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " as in rosita does not move.", "answer": " joey, it\u0092s just a chair! what\u0092s the big deal?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " the big deal is that it is the exact equal distance from the bathroom to the kitchen and it\u0092s at the perfect angle so you don\u0092t get any glare coming of off stevie.", "answer": " stevie the tv?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": "  is there a problem?", "answer": " no!  oh what does he know! come on rosita, us chichas got to stick together!  you bitch!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " hey, y\u0092know what\u0092s weird? after you guys get married, when you introduce me to people you\u0092re gonna have to say, \"this is my brother-in-law ross.\" not, \"my friend ross,\" \"brother-in-law ross.\" that\u0092s weird isn\u0092t it?", "answer": " couldn\u0092t i just say, \"this is ross?\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  hey ross! so, i was checking out the uh, real estate section\u009a", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " oh, it looks like mom and dad\u0092s house. oh, it even has a tree with a broken limb out front and the uh, the window in the attic is\u009aoh my god!!", "answer": " what? what happened to the window in the attic?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe mom and dad are selling the house!", "answer": " i can\u0092t believe they-they didn\u0092t even tell us!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  uh, hello dad! monica and i just saw the house in the paper!  yes we\u0092re surprised!  who did you leave a message with?", "answer": "  sorry!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " joey, joey i am so sorry.", "answer": " i told you not to move it! rach, how would you feel if say, i wanted to move you mom, and you said don\u0092t, and i did it anyway and her head fell off?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " okay, come on\u0097joey, i\u0092ll buy you a new one! all right? we\u0092ll go down to the store right now and we\u0092ll-we\u0092ll get you a new chair.", "answer": "  she\u0092s not even cold yet!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " but don\u0092t you think rosita would\u0092ve wanted you to move on? i mean y\u0092know, she did always put\u009ayour comfort first.", "answer": " that\u0092s true.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  okay? you ready?", "answer": " yeah, i\u009a  i don\u0092t want stevie to see her like this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " i can\u0092t believe we have to say goodbye to the house we grew up in. man, some-some stranger\u0092s gonna be living in my room.", "answer": " well, after 15 years of mom and dad keeping it as a shrine to you, it\u0092s time the velvet ropes came down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " they kept your room for a while.", "answer": " oh please! dad turned my room into a gym 20 minutes after i moved out! i gotta say, a tanning bed and a stack of victoria\u0092s secret catalogues, not a gym!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " come on, you know they love you.", "answer": " as much as they love you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i was their first born! they thought she was barren! it\u0092s not my fault.", "answer": "  hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " ugh, i hate this year!", "answer": " what\u0092s wrong with this year?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " well okay, it\u0092s already february and i\u0092ve only given two massages and they were both the worst tippers in the world!", "answer": " that was me and ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " oh that\u0092s right!", "answer": " hey, y\u0092know if you want to pick up some extra cash? some friends of mine made good money doing telemarketing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " oh that\u0092s a great idea. you\u0092re really good on the phone.", "answer": " yeah and yeah, and it would probably be better than the last telephone job i had. y\u0092know, i probably wouldn\u0092t have to say spank as much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " oh yeah, like you never called!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " so basically this is very easy. you read from the script and try to sell as much toner as you possibly can.", "answer": " okay, i can do that! oh, by the way, i love my office.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  why don\u0092t we do a trial run.", "answer": " oh okay. umm, all right.  hi, this is phoebe from empire office supplies, can i speak to your supply manager please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " i\u0092m the supply manager.", "answer": " umm, okay i would like to talk to you about your toner needs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " we don\u0092t need any toner.", "answer": " oh okay, well i\u0092m sorry to bother you. bye-bye.  yeah you\u0092re right, this is easy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " okay, what was wrong with that call?", "answer": " oh well, all right\u009aum, no offense, but you were kind of rude.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " they\u0092re always going to tell you they don\u0092t need toner, but that\u0092s okay because whatever they say, you can find the answer to it here in this script.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " so, i think you\u0092re ready to sell toner, do you have any last questions?", "answer": " no.  oh wait yes! i do, i do have one question. what is toner?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " dad?", "answer": " i\u0092m here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hi. god, it seems like just yesterday you guys used to come out to watch me work.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " dad, we-we can\u0092t believe you\u0092re selling the house.", "answer": " well, it\u0092s time for a new family to start their memories here and hopefully their check will clear before they find the crack in the foundation and the asbestos in the ceiling.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": "  let\u0092s grab our stuff and get the hell out of here.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry we can\u0092t store your childhood things anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " oh, that\u0092s okay, i can\u0092t wait to see everything again! all of the memories\u009a", "answer": " well, i don\u0092t know what\u0092s in the boxes down here, but i do know there are six or seven easy bake ovens in the attic.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " i used to love to play restaurant.", "answer": " yeah, not as much as you used to love to play uncooked batter eater.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " wow! great!  wait, dad who-who\u0092s cigarettes are these?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know. they-they must be your mother\u0092s, but please, please don\u0092t ask her. i\u0092ll throw these away.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " cool! dad! my report cards! hey, check this out dad,  math, a. science, a. history, a. gym\u009a oooh, my rock polisher!", "answer": " oh look, look there\u0092s your old makeup kit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " it\u0092s a clown kit! clown kit!", "answer": " well, the white seems to be untouched.  uh-oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " y\u0092know how the garage floods every spring?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " how are you ever going to sell this place?", "answer": " i think i accidentally used monica\u0092s boxes to keep the water away from the porsche.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " oh no. dad! dad! what\u009a oh god\u009aeverything\u0092s ruined! dad, she\u0092s gonna be crushed!", "answer": " you don\u0092t secretly smoke do you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " no!", "answer": " so it\u0092s just your mother then.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " i don\u0092t need any toner.", "answer": " i\u0092m hearing what you\u0092re saying, but at our prices everyone needs toner.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " not me.", "answer": " may i ask why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " you wanna know why. you wanna know why?", "answer": " i surely do!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " okay, so\u009ano toner today. thanks anyway, bye-bye.", "answer": " no-no wait-wait! i can\u0092t just let you hang up! just please talk to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " well\u009ai only have one thing to do today.  i guess i could push it back.", "answer": " yeah! now, why do you want to kill yourself?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " it\u0092s just that i uh, have been working for ten years now at this meaningless, dead-end job and nobody here even knows i exist!", "answer": " chandler?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " i-i\u0092m sorry?", "answer": " no look, i-i\u0092m sure that people know you exist!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " you will like it!", "answer": " no i won\u0092t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " you don\u0092t even know!", "answer": " because, i know what i like and what i don\u0092t like! it\u0092s not the same thing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " come on joey, i just bought you a new chair! the most expensive one in the store! hey, y\u0092know what i was thinking? we could name her francette.", "answer": " francette? what is she? a couch?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " poor thing. cut down in her prime.", "answer": " joey, the new chair will be here in an hour. maybe we should actually move rosita out of here. y\u0092know, start the heeling process?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " well, i guess you\u0092re right. maybe, maybe i\u0092ll take her down to the incinerator. it\u0092s gonna be so said, and kinda cool.  she\u0092s heeled!", "answer": " that\u0092s weird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " no it\u0092s not weird, it\u0092s a miracle!", "answer": " it\u0092s not a miracle joey! i\u0092m sure there\u0092s some explanation.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " oh there is! if you want something enough and your heart is pure, wondrous things can happen!", "answer": " joey, i really don\u0092t\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": "  can you tell me how this happened?", "answer": " well no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " miracle!", "answer": " no, y\u0092know what? maybe somebody came in here and fixed it! or something!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " someone like an\u009aangel?", "answer": " that\u0092s right joey, the chair angel came in and heeled your chair.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " well, she\u0092ll understand right? it\u0092s not like i did it on purpose.", "answer": " dad that won\u0092t matter to her. look, all my stuff is safe and dry and all her is-is, is growing new stuff! see, this is exactly the kind of thing that makes her think you guys love me more than you love her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " oh my god, does she really thinks that?", "answer": " well, can you blame her?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " well i don\u0092t know, i-i suppose we may have favored you unconsciously, you were a medical marvel! the doctor said your mother could\u009a", "answer": " dad, dad i don\u0092t want to hear about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " well, not right now. okay look, monica came here for some memories and damnit, we\u0092re gonna give her some! okay, grab\u009agrab some empty boxes. okay? we\u0092ll-we\u0092ll take stuff from mine and whatever we can pass off as hers we\u0092ll-we\u0092ll put \u0091em in their.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " great!", "answer": " like uh y\u0092know like this! this!  she-she could\u0092ve made this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " sure!", "answer": " right? and this!  she-she could\u0092ve won this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": "  this could\u0092ve been hers!", "answer": " sure! ooh-ooh, what about this?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": "  i am so psyched i kept this chair for myself!", "answer": " yeah, me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hey, how\u0092s\u009ahow\u0092s the uh, miracle chair?", "answer": " fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " yeah? wow! y\u0092know, that this thing has speakers in the headrest!", "answer": " no. really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " yeah! you can hook it up to your tv and you get radio!", "answer": "  my chair heels itself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": "  hey guy!", "answer": " wait, what was that? that sounded like someone being nice to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " no! that\u0092s just the \"hey guy\" guy. he says that to everybody! he\u0092s the worst! i\u0092d like to take him with me!", "answer": " all right so earl, let\u0092s just forget about the people at the office, okay? there-there\u0092s gotta be someone else in your life worth sticking around for! what about-what about your family, your friends, or maybe your girlfriend?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  yeah! right!", "answer": " oh sorry, boyfriend!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " oh no.", "answer": " no, whatever! anything! the \"hey guy\" guy: hey guy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " yeah, he\u0092s gotta go.", "answer": " okay, i should, i should probably be getting back to my thing now. see ya.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " no! i\u0092m not finished yet! don\u0092t! don\u0092t you dare hang up on me!!!", "answer": "   the new girl\u0092s good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " hey guys! hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " hey, i just whipped us up some easy bake treats, they should be ready in about three days.", "answer": "  that\u0092s a good one! do you hear that ross? three days!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": "  yeah! yeah!  oh, this will make a great memory.", "answer": "  okay. so, which boxes are mine?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " yeah. yeah, oh you loved that thing. you always had it with you. you never went anywhere without-without that coloring book.", "answer": "  really? wow! it looks like i had some trouble staying inside the lines.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": "  oh, an old glove?", "answer": " oh, yeah you loved that glove! you took it every place you went. you never went any place without that glove.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " oh, i don\u0092t know how that got in there.", "answer": "  this isn\u0092t mine.  hey, this isn\u0092t, this isn\u0092t my stuff! ugh, ross!  these are your boxes! where are my boxes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " umm, your boxes are umm\u009a", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " dad?", "answer": " well, the garage flooded sweetie and it ruined everything in your boxes. i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " just mine?", "answer": " i\u0092m afraid so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " so why-why wasn\u0092t ross\u0092s stuff ruined?  and if you say the words medical marvel i\u0092m going to easy bake your head!", "answer": " well, i used your boxes to divert water away from the porsche.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " so wait, ross\u0092s stuff is fine, but i have no memories because you wanted to keep the bottom two inches of your car away from water!!!", "answer": " there was also leaves and guk and stuff.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " hey chandler!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " how would you like to sit in a chair that fully reclines, has a rolling massage, and speakers in the head rest?", "answer": " yeah, i\u0092d love to but i\u0092ve tried that so many times they won\u0092t even let me in the store anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " well what if i told you, you can do it in my apartment?", "answer": "  are you telling me that you bought the chair that is making all other lounge systems obsolete? the chair that sit magazine called the chair of the year?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " that\u0092s awesome! that\u0092s great! what made you do it?!", "answer": " well, it\u0092s a long story, but umm i broke joey\u0092s chair\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " whoa-whoa-whoa! you broke joey\u0092s chair?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " i thought i broke joey\u0092s chair! that\u0092s why i replaced it with mine!", "answer": " ohhhhh. that\u0092s how it got fixed!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " well, what did you think, that-that elves came in and fixed", "answer": " noo!  angels.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " joey you broke my chair!!", "answer": " your chair?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " yeah, he thought he broke your chair so he switched the chairs!", "answer": " so, there was no miracle?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " no joe, no miracle.", "answer": "  oh no this is devastating! my faith is shaken. i\u0092m so glad i have the new chair to get my through this difficult time in my life.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " uh-huh! nice try, but you don\u0092t get that chair anymore! all right? that is my chair now! you can sit on my lap!  no i take that back!", "answer": " i think i should get the chair!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " how do you figure?", "answer": " because you  broke a chair and you  broke a chair! the only one around here that hasn\u0092t broke a chair, is me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " no-no-no! this chair\u0092s not going anywhere.", "answer": " well, where\u0092s the logic in that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " the logic is, that there are two of us and we are both strong enough to break a chair in half!", "answer": " so joey breaks my chair and i get nothing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " that\u0092s right!", "answer": " what are you guys? like a gang or something?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": "  excuse me! can you tell me where i can find earl? he\u0092s the supply manager around here.", "answer": " sorry, i don\u0092t know any earl.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": "  i\u0092m right here!!!!", "answer": "  earl! i\u0092m phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " phoebe? the lady who sells toner?", "answer": " umm, look it, you-you can\u0092t kill yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": "  look, um i really appreciate your coming down\u009a", "answer": " no-no i can\u0092t! i can\u0092t let you do it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " why?!", "answer": " because it was fate that made me call you today!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 281, "asentId": 282}, {"question": " i thought it was toner.", "answer": " no! think about it okay? this isn\u0092t even my regular job! okay? and my first day on the job, you\u0092re my first call! and-and somebody else might\u0092ve hung up on you, but i wouldn\u0092t do that because i know about this stuff. my mom killed herself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " how?", "answer": " i\u0092m not gonna give you tips! look don\u0092t you see that this-this\u009athis all came together so that i could stop you from doing this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " couldn\u0092t it just be a coincidence?", "answer": " no, it\u0092s fate!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 289, "asentId": 290}, {"question": " it doesn\u0092t really seem like enough to be fate.", "answer": " oh. well umm, okay here\u0092s a weird thing. my mother was also a supply manager.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " i\u0092m actually the office manager.", "answer": " oh my god! so was she! and! get this, okay? your-your name is earl, right? her name was pearl, p-earl.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " well, was there anything else?!", "answer": " sure!  umm, where are you from?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " philadelphia.", "answer": " oh my god! so was she! oh, i\u0092ve got-i\u0092ve got goose bumps.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": "  really?", "answer": " well, y\u0092know i\u0092m wearing layers and it\u0092s warm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " yeah-yeah.", "answer": " but if\u0097no look, okay. these jerks might not care about you, but the universe does! and that says a lot!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": "  did you hear that?! i don\u0092t need you guys to care about me! because the universe cares! the whole universe!   i really wished they\u0092d care just a little bit though.", "answer": " y\u0092know, i don\u0092t-i don\u0092t think it\u0092s you. this is a freaky place.  hey! guys!   oh no, it\u0092s you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " oh, this terrible! everything is destroyed! look at this.  it obviously meant enough for me to save it, and i don\u0092t even know what it is! ohh, it\u0092s still soft.  what do you think this is?", "answer": " all right. i think it was a mouse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": "  how are you honey?", "answer": " how do you think i am?! you\u0092ve wrecked all my childhood memories. you love ross more than me. and i just rubbed a dead mouse on my face!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": "  what\u0092s this?", "answer": " it\u0092s the key to my porsche. well, the key to your porsche.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 313, "asentId": 314}, {"question": "  what?!", "answer": "  what?!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " i\u0092ve been thinking about getting rid of it. i was driving it the other day and saw my reflection in a store window. your mother\u0092s right, i do look like an ass.", "answer": " wait, you\u0092re giving me your porsche, you\u0092re kidding me right?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 317, "asentId": 318}, {"question": " well w-w-w-w-wait, w-wait, wait, wait a minute! i mean a couple of stupid boxes get wet and she gets a porsche?!", "answer": "  why don\u0092t we take it for a spin?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 319, "asentId": 320}, {"question": " all right!", "answer": " well, what about me?! i\u0092m a medical marvel!! ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}, {"question": " oh yeah.", "answer": " ahhhh\u009a.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 323, "asentId": 324}, {"question": " ahhh\u009a\u009a  eh?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 325, "asentId": 326}, {"question": "  hey guys!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 327, "asentId": 328}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " do you guys know what happened to chandler\u0092s barca lounger?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 329, "asentId": 330}, {"question": " oh yeah, joey broke it. had to get rid of it.", "answer": " are you kidding?! i get a porsche and the barca lounger\u0092s gone?! this is the best day ever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 331, "asentId": 332}]